megrisoft.com 2019-05-19

# Megrisoft Privacy Policy at Megrisoft.Com

In our privacy policy when we use “Megrisoft” refers to all websites ( megrisoft.co.in, megrisoft.co.uk, megrisoft.ca ) mobile sites, applications, and other properties or services owned or operated by Megri Soft Limited. When you use Megrisoft services or web properties , you trust us with your information. Megri Soft Ltd (“we”, “us”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with the Terms of Use and other documents referred to in them) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

This Website is owned and operated by or on behalf of Megri Soft Limited (“We”, “Us” and “Our”, as appropriate in the context). We are registered as a public limited company under Indian Company Act number 547495 and Our registered office is at SCO 80 Sector 47 Chandigarh India 160047

### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

Our Privacy Policy explains What information/ data we collect and why we do it, How we use that information/ data and update information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the Policies of companies that Megrisoft does not own or control, or to individuals whom Megrisoft does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties to which Megrisoft may disclose user information as set forth in this Policy.

### User Personal Data Protection Policy

This web page describes Megri Soft Limited privacy policies with concern to the collection of data, usage and any disclosure of any personally-identifiable information (referred to as ‘personal information’) you provide to any of our mobile applications.

While accessing our any mobile application, web sites or any other related services (collectively referred and named as ‘Services’) you hereby consent to the collection, manipulation, storage, transfer, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this User Personal Data Protection Policy. If you do not agree to our this policy, please we request you not to use any of our Mobile Applications and websites.

### Gathering Information

#### Getting Personal Information

Personal information is the data which provides user identity that can be used to contact you whether offline or online. We get your personal information during:

  * The sign up, sign in or any modifications of an account on any of our applications
  * While creating a personal profile or account on our applications
  * Request for the service from third party service providers on our site or accessing to our services on social networks and other third party services
  * While requesting for any technical support services, subscription to our newsletters or any other marketing related services such as email campaigns

The collected information can also vary. Such user information can include but not limited only to the user name, phone number, email address, date of birth, home address, country, gender or mobile phone number. Additional and optional information you willingly include but are not limited to a short description of your biography or a personal photo or image (or avatar). Doing same will enhance your user experience at any of our mobile applications, adding a more personalized touch to your app profile. You can choose to go out of this at any time by deleting this optional or additional information.

### Consequences with not providing Personal Information

If app user will opt not to give his/ her Personal Information that is necessary or mandatory to give for processing your request, then we can not be able to provide the corresponding service on your device.

### Collection of Information Automatically

In addition to information given by user while accessing any of our application, the Application can collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the mobile device you use, unique device ID of your mobile devices, IP address of your mobile device, your operating system of mobile, the type of Internet browsers you use on mobile, and the information about the way you use the mobile application and the location of your mobile device.

### Opt-out Rights of User

You can stop collection of information by any of our application easily by uninstalling the Application. You can use the standard uninstall processes available in your mobile device or by mobile application marketplace. User can also send request to opt-out via email, at [Support@megrisoft.com](mailto:Support@megrisoft.com).

### Do Third Parties see or have any access to the information obtained from application?

Only aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services for  helping us in improving our Application and services. We will only share user  information with the third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

  * as required by the law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or any similar legal process;

  * when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is important to protect our user rights, protect your safety or the safety of any others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf for our clients;

  * will never have an independent use to the user information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adopt to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.

### Policy for Data Retention and Managing Your Information

We will keep data provided by User for as long as you use our any of the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain User collected information for up to 24 months automatically and thereafter may store it in aggregate or our collection.

If you would like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via any of our mobile application, please get in touch with us at [support@megrisoft.com](mailto:support@megrisoft.com) and we will respond to your email within few time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data or information may be required in order for the mobile application to function properly and smoothly.

### Children

We do not use the Mobile Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a guardian  or a parent gets aware that his or her child has given us with the information without coming into their knowledge or their consent, then he or she should contact us at [support@megrisoft.com](mailto:support@megrisoft.com). We will delete this kind of information from our files as soon as possible.

### Security

We are always concerned with the confidentiality and safeguarding of your information. We provide physical and procedural safeguards to protect user information we keep, process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this user information to authorized employees, vendors and contractors who need to know that user information in order to operate, develop or improve our mobile application. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security to user information we use, process and maintain, but no security system can make its prevention from all potential security breaches.

### Your Consent

By using any of our site or any mobile application, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

### Any Changes in Privacy Policy

If we make any changes in our privacy policy from as and when required anytime, the we will publish those changes on this web page, and/or update modification date of the the Privacy Policy.

### **Contact Us**

If you have any queries regarding our application privacy while using the Application, or have any questions about our practices, please get in touch with us via email at [Support@megrisoft.com](mailto:Support@megrisoft.com).
